If a person offered you money to leave a suitcase in your space, would you accept?
如果一个人给你钱，让你把一个手提箱放在你的空间里，你会接受吗？
And in return, if you had too many items, would you consider trusting someone you‘ve met on the internet for safekeeping?
反过来呢：如果你有太多的物品，你会考虑信任在网上认识的人，让他们保管这些物品吗？
Anthony Paine believes enough of us would answer ‘yes‘ to both to have founded his startup Stashbee.
安东尼·佩恩相信我们中有足够多的人会对这些问题回答“是”，于是他创办了自己的初创公司Stashbee。
His business connects people with spare room to those with a storage need.
他的业务将有闲置空间的人与有存储需求的人联系了起来。
And it's just one player in the booming ’sharing economy‘, an industry that relies on people renting out things like their beds, bikes and even parking spaces.
而这只是蓬勃发展的“共享经济”中的一员，共享经济这个行业依赖于人们出租像他们的床、自行车甚至停车位之类的东西。
Airbnb, a company valued at 200bn RMB, provides a platform for those renting property short-term.
估值达2000亿人民币的爱彼迎公司，为那些短期租赁房产的人提供了一个平台。
DogVacay pairs holidaymaking pet owners with pet-friendly hosts, and aims to be profitable by 2017.
狗狗度假屋将度假的宠物主人与喜爱宠物的房东配对，目标是在2017年实现盈利。
All their business models revolve around a simple word: trust.
他们所有的商业模式都围绕着一个简单的词：信任。
So, could Stashbee measure up?
那么，Stashbee能够胜任吗？
BBC reporter Dougal Shaw decided to try it out for himself.
英国广播公司记者杜格尔·肖决定亲自试一试。
He had some odds and ends to store while renovating his house and found a host through the website who would store them for 475 RMB for two months.
他在装修房子的时候有一些零碎物品需要存放，通过该网站他找到了一位房东，房东可以以475元人民币的价格为他保管两个月。
The process was relatively smooth and hassle-free.
整个过程相对顺利，没有什么麻烦。
Heavyweights in the traditional storage industry, such as Big Yellow and Access, aren't convinced.
传统存储行业的巨头，比如大黄蜂和爱可赛斯，并不服气。
A representative from Access told Shaw he was sceptical about storing with “amateurs”.
爱可赛斯的一位代表告诉肖，他对把物品存放在“业余人士”那里持怀疑态度。
He cited 24/7 access to the items and better security as the main advantages of his service.
他提到随时可以取用物品以及更好的安全性是他们服务的主要优势。
Cost-wise it would set you back an extra 160 RMB to store with them.
从成本方面来看，在他们那里存储物品会让你多花费160元人民币。
Stashbee agree that tackling security concerns is important, but say business success depends more on people overcoming a distrust of strangers we've been taught since childhood.
Stashbee认同解决安全问题很重要，但同时表示商业成功更多地取决于人们克服从小就被灌输的对陌生人的不信任。
They aren't alone. Companies such as Costockage, Roost and Spacer all run similar storage businesses, and are all banking on a shift in consumer attitudes.
还有其他像Costockage、Roost和Spacer等公司都经营着类似的存储业务，并且都指望消费者态度的转变。
And the concept of social storage doesn't stop there.
而且社交存储的概念并不止于此。
CityStasher believe there's a gap in the market for those who want to store things for extremely short periods of time.
城市储物柜公司认为，对于那些想要极短时间存储物品的人来说，市场上存在着一个空白。
For example, if you have three hours to kill in a city before your train leaves, what do you do with your suitcase?
例如，如果你在火车出发前在一个城市有三个小时的空闲时间，你会怎么处理你的手提箱呢？
CityStasher hope you will choose to leave it at a local newsagent, found through their website of course, rather than in the station's pricier left luggage office.
城市储物柜公司希望你会选择把它放在通过他们的网站找到的当地报刊亭，当然，而不是放在车站更贵的行李寄存处。
Would you try it out?
你会试一试吗？
It's a question of trust.
这是一个关于信任的问题。